This is...
（岡部倫太郎(おかべりんたろう)）これは…
A time machine.
（阿万音鈴羽(あまねすずは)）タイムマシン
I'm from the year 2036.
私は2036年から来たんだ
Suzuha...
（岡部）鈴羽…
私がタイムトラベラー
I'm the time traveler...
ジョン･タイターだよ
John Titor.
Missing Link
Necrosis
～
In the year 2036,
（鈴羽）2036年 世界は
ＳＥＲＮ(セルン)に支配されていた
the world is ruled by SERN.
It's an oppressive, totalitarian society— a dystopia.
そこは徹底した管理社会
ディストピア
People were robbed of their freedom,
人々は自由を奪われ
死んだように暮らしてる
and they live like zombies.
逆らう者は皆 殺された
Anyone who disobeyed was killed.
私は そんな
ＳＥＲＮの支配から―
I was part of the resistance,
fighting to free the world from SERN's control.
人々を解放するために戦う
レジスタンスの一員だった
（鈴羽）ああ… あっ うっ！
ふっ！
（鈴羽）
この死んだような世界を
変えるため
To change this forsaken world...
...I entered the time machine my father left me.
私は 父さんが残してくれた
タイムマシンに乗り込んだ
（鈴羽）そして…
It was all to change the future.
未来を変えるために
Then everything you wrote on @channel...
では「アットチャンネル」に
書き込んだことは すべて…
Yes, most of it was true.
（鈴羽）
うん ほとんどは真実
But SERN is a research organization,
（牧瀬紅莉栖(まきせくりす)）だけど
ＳＥＲＮは研究機関であって―
権力を持つ
統治機関じゃないわ
not a ruling body.
On the net, I told John Titor that many times.
私は何度もネット上で
ジョン･タイターに そう訴えてきた
待て！
Wait!
Does that mean you
…ということは お前―
are Chestnut Rice and Kamehameha?
あのとき
「アットチャンネル」にいた―
栗悟飯(くりごはん)とカメハメ波(は)か？
Titor identified himself,
（紅莉栖）タイターの中の人が
名乗り出たんだから―
so it wouldn't be fair if I didn't, right?
私も名乗り出ないと
フェアじゃないでしょ？
ハア… ならば 俺もならおう
Then I'll identify myself as well.
I was using the trip Hououin Kyouma—
俺は鳳凰院凶真(ほうおういんきょうま)という真名(まな)で…
We know that.
（紅莉栖･鈴羽）それは知ってる
あっ…
SERN succeeded in developing a time machine.
ＳＥＲＮは
タイムマシンの開発に成功したの
Since they were the only ones able to
時間という
４つ目の次元に干渉できる―
interfere with the fourth dimension, time,
唯一の存在となったことで
世界の秩序を塗り替えた
they remade the world map, so to speak,
and Makise Kurisu is the one
そして 牧瀬紅莉栖は―
who contributed the most to the time machine's development.
ＳＥＲＮのタイムマシン開発に
最も貢献した人物―
She's hailed as the mother of the time machine.
“タイムマシンの母”として
あがめられている
I worked with SERN?
私がＳＥＲＮに協力？
冗談じゃないわ
No way!
Why would I work with people who perform human experiments?
人体実験までするような連中に
なんで私が？
That's what happened in the future.
（鈴羽）未来では そうなっていた
（紅莉栖）あっ…
So that's why you disliked me...
それで私のこと 目の敵(かたき)に？
（岡部）ん…
What about the future me?
ならば 未来の俺は？
Okabe Rintarou is a famous terrorist.
（鈴羽）岡部倫太郎は
テロリストとして有名
Terrorist?
（岡部）テロ？
A terrorist who fought SERN.
（鈴羽）
ＳＥＲＮにたてついた
テロリスト
And you're both...
そして 君たちは…
２人とも
2036年には死亡している
...dead in the year 2036.
（紅莉栖）あっ
（岡部）あ…
I need to hurry.
（鈴羽）もう行かないと
（岡部）待て！
Wait.
You said something crazy like that,
そんな とんでもないことだけ
言い残して―
then you're just going to return to the future?
未来へ帰るつもりか？
That's why I'm leaving.
（鈴羽）だから行くの
I'm going to the past to change the future.
そんな未来を変えるために過去へ
To 1975...
1975年へ
えっ… 1975年？
1975?
ＳＥＲＮがタイムマシン開発に
成功したのは―
SERN succeeded in developing the time machine
due to the time machine created in Akihabara in 2010.
2010年に秋葉原(あきはばら)で作られた
タイムマシンがあったから
You mean the Phone Microwave?
（紅莉栖）電話レンジのこと？
うん
SERN used a communication monitoring system
ＳＥＲＮは
通信傍受システムを使って―
to gather all the information they could on time machines from around the world.
世界中から タイムマシンに関する
あらゆる情報を集めていた
そのシステムに
岡部倫太郎―
I think the first D-mail you sent tripped the system.
君が最初に送ったＤメールが
引っ掛かったんだと思う
The message I sent in front of the radio building?
ラジ館前で送った
あのメールが…
Yes.
（鈴羽）そう
So if we delete the message from SERN's database...
だから ＳＥＲＮのデータベースに
残っている―
そのメールを消しさえすれば
未来は変わる
...the future will change.
（岡部）あっ…
We can go to the beta world line,
（鈴羽）
ＳＥＲＮがタイムマシンの開発に
成功しなかった―
where SERN never created a time machine.
ベータ世界線へ
行くことができる
Will that save Mayuri?
そうすれば
まゆりも助かるのか？
（鈴羽）ん… 多分
Probably.
Then we should start hacking SERN's database immediately...
だったら すぐにでも―
ＳＥＲＮのデータベースに
ハッキングをかけて…
We need the IBN 5100 for that.
（鈴羽）
それにはＩＢＮ5100が必要
そうか それで…
I see. So that's why...
My task was to go to 1975,
私の使命は1975年に行って
ＩＢＮ5100を手に入れ―
find an IBN 5100,
岡部倫太郎に託すこと
and get it to Okabe Rintarou,
なっ…
but I stayed too long to look for my father.
なのに 父さんを捜そうとして
この時代に長居しすぎた
I should've left earlier.
もっと早く行くべきだったのに
（鈴羽）あっ！
（紅莉栖）あっ 大丈夫？
Is everything okay?
（鈴羽）あっ…
It's...
そんな… 壊れてる
It's broken.
（岡部）えっ
（紅莉栖）あ…
（岡部）ハッ
This is bad!
（岡部）マズい
（紅莉栖）どうする？
What do we do?
俺が なんとかする
I'll think of something.
You hide.
２人は隠れて！
隙を見て逃げろ
Run when you can.
Anyone here?
（警官Ａ）誰かいるのか？
Who's there?
（警官Ａ）誰だ？
（岡部）近づくな！
Stay back!
I'm in the middle of an operation
機関の謀略を阻止するための
作戦行動中だ！
to end the Organization's schemes!
This is a level 17 top secret mission,
これはレベル17の
極秘ミッションである
分かったら即刻 離れるがいい！
こっちだ 急げ！
so stay away from this place!
This way! Hurry!
（警官Ａ）あっ コラ！
（警官Ｂ）待ちなさい
Hey!
Wait!
We're running.
（紅莉栖）逃げるわよ！
（鈴羽）あっ…
（紅莉栖）早く！
（鈴羽）あ…
Hurry!
I don't know what happened in the future,
未来じゃ どうだったか
知らないけど―
but right now, I'm a lab member, just like you!
今の私は
あなたと同じラボメンなのよ！
ハッ　ん…
（警官たちの荒い息）
（岡部）ハアッ フウ…
（紅莉栖）岡部！
Okabe!
無事だったか？ 逃げるぞ！
You're safe?
Let's go!
（パトカーのサイレン）
（紅莉栖）どうする？
もう あそこには戻れないわよ
What do we do?
We can't go back there.
Was the time machine broken?
（岡部）タイムマシンは
壊れていたのか？
Was it from when it crashed into the roof?
（紅莉栖）
屋上に衝突した衝撃で？
It didn't crash.
（鈴羽）
あれは衝突したんじゃないよ
There was an error in calculating the coordinates
座標計算に誤差があったせいで
あの位置に出現しちゃっただけ
so it appeared there.
着いたときは
壊れていなかった
When I arrived, it wasn't broken.
（岡部）だったら いつ？
Then when?
If I had to guess, I'd say that thunderstorm we had...
考えられるとすれば
この前の雷雨
ハッ！
（鈴羽）落雷したか
それとも浸水したか
It might've been hit by lightning or flooded...
（岡部）ハッ… 俺のせいだ
It's my fault.
Because I stopped you then...
俺があの夜
引き止めたせいで…
タイムリープマシンで
I'll use the time leap machine...
We can only use it to go back 48 hours.
それじゃあ 最大48時間までしか
さかのぼれない
あ… あの夜までは届かない
We can't get back to that night.
Okarin!
（椎名(しいな)まゆり）あー オカリン
（岡部）あっ
And Kurisu and Suzu are with you!
（まゆり）紅莉栖ちゃんと
鈴(すず)さんも一緒だ
You didn't go home?
（岡部）お前たち
帰ったのではなかったのか？
Mayushii said we should have a party to celebrate the time machine's completion after all.
（橋田 至(はしだいたる)）
まゆ氏が やっぱり完成祝い
するべきって言うから
Daru and I went shopping!
ダル君と２人で
買い出しをしてきたのです
I said we were done for the day!
（岡部）今日は解散と言っただろ！
（まゆり）ああ…
（紅莉栖）ごめんね まゆり
I'm sorry, Mayuri.
We have to talk about something important.
これから 私たち
重要な話をする予定だったの
Okarin?
オカリン？
とにかく
今日のところは帰ってくれ
Just go home for today.
We'll have the party another time.
完成祝いは また改めてやろう
All right.
分かった
でも 危ないことはしないでね
But don't do anything dangerous.
Mayushii is worried.
まゆしぃは心配なのです
大丈夫だ　約束する
It'll be fine.
I promise.
うん
See you tomorrow then!
それじゃあ またあした
Yeah.
ああ
（パトカーのサイレン）
（通行人Ａ）電車 止まってるって
（通行人Ｂ）マジか
I heard the trains stopped.
Seriously?
ハッ！
We'll have to repair the time machine.
タイムマシンを修理するしかない
ウフフッ
First, go back five hours ago,
（紅莉栖）まず 今から５時間前
when the time leap machine was completed.
つまり タイムリープマシンの
完成した時間まで飛ぶ
From there, go back 48 hours
そこから 改めて48時間
11日の14時まで飛ぶ
to 2:00 PM on the 11th.
That's the most time we have.
それが 今の私たちが使える
最大の時間ってわけだね
I'll finish the time machine during those two days,
その二日のあいだに―
何としてでも
タイムマシンを修理する
no matter what.
If I can't, I'll redo those two days as many times as it takes.
できなければ
何度でも その二日をやり直す
This isn't to save the world.
（岡部）これは
世界を救うためなのではない
It's a mission to save Mayuri.
まゆりを助けるための
ミッションだ
（岡部）ハッ！
Okabe?
（紅莉栖）岡部？ どうしたの？
What's wrong?
Gather all the lab members right away.
（岡部）至急 ラボメンに
招集をかけてくれ
There's something I want to talk to them about.
聞いてもらいたいことがある
Future tech is great.
（橋田）未来人 すげえ
マジ ぱねえっす
This must be photoshopped.
Can you fix it?
（岡部）直せるか？
Miss Amane, you can't do it yourself?
（橋田）
阿万音氏 自分では無理なん？
私には ちんぷんかんぷん
I really can’t.
My father's the one who made it.
作ったのは父さんだから
There's no way we can fix a time machine from 2036
2036年のタイムマシンを
現代の技術で直せるわけ…
using today's tech—
（岡部）
やってみなければ 分からん
We won't know until we try.
とにかく 二日で
なんとかしてくれ ダル
Anyway, try to do it in two days, Daru.
You're our only hope.
お前だけが頼りだ
（橋田）なんで 二日なん？
（岡部）あっ
Why two days?
ん… それは…
Well...
Just do it!
とにかく 二日だ
If you can, I'll do anything you want.
もし二日で直せたら
何でも言うことを聞いてやる
Teacher, I want to have a day long date with Feyris!
（橋田）
先生！ フェイリスたんと―
１日デートがしたいです！
All right. I'll make it happen somehow.
（岡部）
分かった なんとかしよう
いや… 無理っしょ
No, that's impossible.
I can do anything!
俺に不可能はない　信じろ
Believe in me.
ん…
マジ？ 絶対？
You're serious? For real?
約束する
だから やってくれ
I promise,
so do it.
（橋田）ん…
Very well!
いいですとも！
あっ　あと もう１ついい？
One more thing, okay?
（鈴羽）あっ
If I fix it, in addition to the IBN 5100...
無事に直ったら
ＩＢＮ5100と一緒に―
...get me a cel from the legendary
75年の伝説の魔法もの
「ラジカル少女オミットちゃん」の
セル画も持ってかえってきて
1975 magical girl anime, Ragical Girl Omit!
（岡部）自重しろ
Get to work.
私も手伝おうか？
Should I help too?
No, you need to finish the time leap machine.
（岡部）いや お前には―
タイムリープマシンを
完成させるという重要な仕事がある
We should get back to the la—
そろそろ
ラボに戻ったほうがいい…
Hey, aren't you all forgetting something?
（まゆり）ねえ みんな
もう１つ何か忘れてない？
We should look for Suzu's dad.
鈴さんのお父さん捜し
（鈴羽）父さんのことは もういい
（まゆり）よくないよ！
I'm all right—
No, you're not!
You got in the time machine
鈴さんがタイムマシンに乗ったのは
使命とかもあるけど―
because you had a job to do,
but you also wanted to see your dad, right?
やっぱり お父さんに
会いたかったからなんでしょ？
だったら まゆしぃは
会わせてあげたいのです
So Mayushii wants to help you find him.
Your dad's name was Barrel Titor, right?
父親の名前は
バレル･タイターだったな？
それはコードネーム
本名は知らない
That was his code name.
I don't know his real name.
Where's "Amane" from?
阿万音っていうのは？
From my mother.
母さんの名前
My only clue is this little badge he had.
手がかりは父さんの形見の
このピンバッジだけ
Your dad is in 2010's Akihabara, right?
お父さんは
2010年の秋葉原にいるんだよね？
Okay, Mayushii will be the investigator.
それじゃあ まゆしぃは
早速 捜査を開始するのです！
Shiina Mayuri... is a good girl, isn't she?
椎名まゆり　いい子だね
（岡部）うっ…
（橋田）ふーん
Think you can fix it?
（鈴羽）直りそう？
I can't say for sure,
いや まだ確証はないけど…
but looking at it, I guess...
ただ ちょっと触ってみて
気付いたんだけど―
...it's kind of like the Phone Microwave.
これって
電話レンジと似てるかも
Then it's possible you can fix it, right?
じゃあ 直る可能性は
あるってことだね？
（橋田）うん
（鈴羽）ウフッ
I wonder if your dad's nearby.
（橋田）阿万音氏の親父(おやじ)さんって
僕たちの近くにいるのかな？
He knew that we were in Akiba in 2010, right?
2010年に僕たちが
このアキバにいるって―
知ってたんだよね？
（鈴羽）多分…
直接 聞いたわけじゃないから
I think so,
but I never heard from him directly.
私 父さんには会ったことないし
I've never met him.
Everything was in his will.
全部 父さんの遺書に
書いてあったんだ
My dad was researching a time machine separately from SERN...
父さんはＳＥＲＮとは別に
タイムマシンの研究をしてたの
...to change the future.
未来を変えるためにね
I'm here to carry on his legacy.
私は その遺志を継いで ここにいる
I really am sorry...
（橋田）正直 すまんかった
ああ でも―
But if I can fix the time machine, it's possible that
タイムマシンが直れば
なんとかなるって
1975年から戻ってくるまでに
親父さん 捜しておくから
we'll find your dad before you get back from 1975.
だから オカリンには内緒で
伝説のアニメ「ラジ…」
So keep this a secret from Okarin
and try to get me that cel...
That's a pretty straightforward way to do it.
（紅莉栖）ずいぶんと地道ね
Supposedly, we're the Future Gadget Lab,
仮にも 未来ガジェット研究所
なんだから―
もっと未来的な方法はないの？
yet you don't have a more futuristic way?
そんな都合のいいものはない
Nothing's as convenient.
フウ…
Future Gadget #2, alt. edition.
“未来ガジェット２号
オルタナティブエディション”
Version 2.67.
“バージョン2,67”
AKA the Bamboo Copter Camera.
（岡部）通称「タケコプカメラー」
There's a CCD camera on the lower body.
ＣＣＤカメラが
本体下部に搭載されている
Surprisingly practical.
意外と まともそう
Could we use this for an aerial search?
これで
上空から捜すっていうのは？
The camera spins too,
カメラも一緒に回るので
撮影された映像も高速回転している
so the video you receive revolves at a high speed.
You're at version 2.67, and that still isn't fixed?
バージョン2,67で
そんな不具合が直ってないの？
That's the first one we’ve made.
それが初号機だ
Daru came up with the name, along with the version.
ネーミングはバージョンも含めて
ダルの趣味で―
There's no real meaning.
特に意味はない
（紅莉栖）あっ…
（岡部）ダルは？
Where's Daru?
He's still hard at work.
（鈴羽）
まだ残って作業を続けてる
（岡部）ん？
The Divergence Meter...
（岡部）
ダイバージェンスメーター
（鈴羽）やっぱり これは―
You made it, so I think you should have it.
作った本人である君に
預けておこうと思って
この数字が１％を突破さえできたら
未来は変わる
If this number goes above 1%, the future will change.
それを認識できるのは―
You're the only one who will know,
with your Reading Steiner.
リーディング･シュタイナーの
能力を持った君だけ
Did I give you that before I died in the future?
未来の俺は 死ぬ前に
それをお前に託したのか？
No, I never met you.
ううん
私は一度も会ったことはない
You were a founding member of the resistance I was in.
君はさ 私が所属している
レジスタンスの―
設立メンバーだったんだよ
レジスタンスを設立
フッ くだらない
I founded the resistance?
How stupid.
I couldn't even save Mayuri,
まゆりを助けることもできず
のうのうと生き続けたあげく―
and I kept on living
like a stupid little kid with his fantasies?
そんな厨二病(ちゅうにびょう)みたいなマネを！
It wasn't stupid!
（鈴羽）くだらなくない！
世界に自由を取り戻そうとする
勇敢で立派な志だよ！
It was an honest, brave desire to save the world!
ハッ…
（岡部）あー
ヘイ！ マスター
Hey, mister...
うっ… アイ アム
マッドサイエンティスト
I am mad scientist!
It's so cool!
イッツ ソー クール
You sonuvabitch.
サノバビッチ！
Yes, what is it?
（露天商）ハイ！ 何ですか？
（岡部）ハアッ
日本語でオーケーか
So Japanese works, huh?
ちょっと聞きたいことがある
これに見覚えは？
There's something I want to ask you.
Ever seen this before?
I want to know where it came from.
これの出どころが知りたい
調べることはできないか？
Can you look into it for me?
（露天商）オウ 思い出し…
The remember.
ソーリー
ちょっと難しいですね
Sorry, it's difficult.
Are you sure Japanese works?
日本語 あんまり
オーケーじゃないんじゃない？
フウ… 思い出したら
ここに連絡をくれ
If you remember, contact me here.
（岡部）もしかして
近い未来に作られる物で―
Maybe this’ll be created in the near future,
but it doesn't exist now?
今は まだ存在しないんだろうか？
Maybe it's fate that I never meet my dad, after all.
（鈴羽）やっぱりさ
父さんとは会えない運命なのかも
もう やめにしない？
Want to give up on it?
You're giving up?
あきらめるのか？
まだ あと１日残っているんだぞ！
We still have a day!
What are you—
（鈴羽）何 怒って…
（岡部）俺だって―
I want to prioritize saving Mayuri!
まゆりを助けることを
何より優先したい
Even so, you're a lab member and a friend.
それでも お前は
ラボメンであり 仲間だ
I want to help you if I can!
その仲間が困っているんだから
助けたい！
So why are you already giving up?
それなのに―
お前が真っ先にあきらめて
どうする？
D-Don't yell at me, okay?
ど… どなんないでよ
（岡部）おっ…
I'm sorry.
すまん
Please!
（まゆり）お願いしまーす
（岡部）ん？
（まゆり）お願いしまーす！
（岡部）あいつ 何を？
Please!
What is she...
（まゆり）
先日 誘拐事件が起きちゃいました
There was a kidnapping yesterday!
I'm looking for the criminal. He wore a badge like this!
このピンバッジを付けた犯人を
捜してまーす
ご協力 よろしくお願いしまーす
Please help us!
ん？ ああ オカリーン
Oh, Okarin!
（まゆり）見て見て
（岡部）ん…
Look! Look!
ハアッ まゆり…
Mayuri...
（まゆり）エヘヘ
いい作戦でしょう？
Good idea, right?
まゆしぃのアイデアなのです
It was Mayushii's idea!
これなら みんな“お！”って
思ってくれるかなって
I think everyone might go, "Huh?" when they see this.
Operation name:
作戦名は
「まゆしぃ チラシで大勝利」
Big Victory with Mayushii's Pamphlets!
誘拐事件ってのは
さすがに言いすぎなんじゃ…
I think a kidnapping is pushing it, don't you?
What if the police starts looking for us?
警察に目をつけられたら
どうする？
うっ おっ… マズい
Oh, no! Run!
（岡部）逃げるぞ！
（まゆり）えっ 何？
What?
（警官Ａ）ちょっと 君たち
Hey, you guys!
（警官Ｂ）
あっ コラッ 待ちなさい！
Wait!
（岡部）
ううっ… ハアッ ハアッ
I'm sorry.
（まゆり）ごめんなさい
From now on, ask me about these operations first.
（岡部）
次からは作戦名も含めて
事前に俺に相談するんだな
That includes the name.
（岡部）うっ… ハッ！
What are you doing?
何やってんの？
Oh, it's Christina.
何だ クリスティーナか
Good timing.
（紅莉栖）ちょうどよかったわ
大変なことが分かったの
I heard something pretty serious.
何だ？
What?
When I went to buy lunch, I overheard the clerks.
（紅莉栖）
お昼 買いに行ったら―
店員が話してるのを
聞いちゃったんだけど―
Amane's dad might be a kidnapper.
阿万音さんのお父さん
誘拐犯かも
（まゆり）あ…
（岡部）え？
（まゆり）ああ…
（紅莉栖）えっ？
（まゆり･鈴羽）フフッ
Wh-What?
何？ どういうこと？
What's going on?
（まゆり）フフフッ
How's it going?
（岡部）調子は？
（橋田）ん？
（岡部）差し入れだ
Something to drink.
If you were awesome, you would've brought me
ここはキンキンに冷えた
ノンカロリーのコーラだろ―
an ice-cold zero-calorie cola.
常識的に考えて
（紅莉栖）どう？
タイムマシンは直りそう？
Well?
Can we fix the time machine?
Probably by tomorrow.
（橋田）
あしたまでには なんとか
You worked this whole time, but that's still amazing!
すごいね！
突貫工事とはいえ
Daru's the real deal.
（岡部）ダルの実力は折り紙付きだ
Even if he looks unhealthy and kind of dim.
（鈴羽）見た目は不摂生そうで
さえない感じなのにね
見た目で判断するな
Don't judge him by his looks.
Yeah, I've changed my mind about him.
うん 考えを改める
それじゃあ 阿万音氏も手伝って
Then you can help me too.
Then, in the steaming-hot confines of the time machine,
そして 狭いタイムマシンの中
うだるような暑さに―
僕らは恥ずかしさも忘れて
服を脱ぎ ハア…
we can forget our shame and take off our clothes...
Shut up, pervert!
（紅莉栖）自重しろ！ 変態
Daru and Suzu look good together.
ダル君と鈴さんって
結構 お似合いだね
はあ？ お似合いか？
どの辺がだ？
They do? How?
I don't really know how to say it...
（まゆり）
どの辺って言えないけど
何となく
They just do.
（鈴羽）あっ どうしたの？
（岡部）気にするな
What's up?
Don't worry about it!
Mayuri was just saying something weird.
まゆりが
おかしなことを言っただけだ
But if the time machine gets fixed,
でも タイムマシンが直ったら―
乗っていっちゃう鈴さんが心配だな
I'm worried about Suzu when she rides it!
２人乗りなら まゆしぃが―
If it could fit two people, I could go with you...
一緒に行ってあげられるのに
お前が一緒に行ってどうするのだ？
Why would you go with her?
Why else?
決まってるよ
I'd hold Suzu's hand really tight, and I'd say,
鈴さんの手をムギューっと
握ってね
“大丈夫 まゆしぃが一緒だから
大丈夫だよ”って―
"It's okay! Mayushii's with you, so it's okay!"
応援してあげるの
（鈴羽）エヘッ
Hey, I'm saying this because
（鈴羽）あのさ 今 言わないと―
I don't think I'll ever have the chance to say it again.
機会を永遠に逃しちゃいそうだから
言うけど…
What? That's an exaggeration.
（岡部）何だ？ 大げさだな
I'm really grateful to you all.
（鈴羽）私さ 君たちには
ホント感謝してるんだ
（岡部）ん？
初めて この時代に来たとき
知ってる人は誰もいなくて―
When I first came here, I didn't know anyone.
Even though this era is much more peaceful,
この時代のほうが
すごく平和なのにさ
なんだか
私にとっては すごく怖かった
somehow, to me, it was really scary...
But now I have lots of friends.
でも 今は こうして
たくさんの仲間ができた
I'm really happy that I could come here...
この時代に来ることができて
君たちと同じ時間が過ごせて―
and that I could spend time with you guys.
私 ホントに楽しかった
I'm glad I had the chance to be a lab member, if only for a little while.
ほんのちょっとでも
ラボメンの一員になれて よかった
I'm glad I had the chance to spend time with you all...
君たちと一緒にいられて
よかった
鈴羽
Suzuha...
Okabe Rintarou!
（鈴羽）岡部倫太郎
（岡部）ん？
Change the future...
きっと未来を変えてね
Make it a free world, like this one!
今みたいな
自由な世界に変えて！
鈴羽…
Suzuha?
（岡部）あっ
Yes?
はい　ん？
Hello?
（男）アロー？
マッドサイエンティスト？
Mad scientist so cool?
ソー クール？
あっ 昼間の露天商か？
The street vendor from this morning?
I remembered...
（露天商）私 思い出しましたね
イエスタデイ ナイト
ピンバッジの男
About the man with that pin badge...
（岡部）
父親が分かったということか？
You found her father?
I'll be right there!
すぐに行く！ 待ってろ
Please wait!
～